[
  {
    "question": "\nWhat's the correct way to display `Hello world`?\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```js\nconsole.log(\"Hello world\");\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```py\nprint(\"Hello world\")\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```c\nprintf(\"Hello world\");\n```", "order": 2 },
      {
        "code": "```java\nSystem.out.println(\"Hello world\");\n```",
        "order": 3
      },
      { "code": "```ruby\nputs \"Hello world\"\n```", "order": 4 },
      { "code": "```php\n<?php echo 'Hello World'; ?>\n```", "order": 5 }
    ],
    "results": {
      "correct": [0, 1, 2, 3, 4],
      "incorrect": [],
      "misbehaved": [5]
    }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nHow do you remove a table named `freeCoedCamp` using SQL?\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```sql\nREMOVE TABLE freeCodeCamp;\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```sql\nDROP TABLE freeCodeCamp;\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```sql\nDESTROY TABLE freeCodeCamp;\n```", "order": 2 },
      { "code": "```sql\nðŸ§¨TABLE freeCodeCamp;\n```", "order": 3 },
      { "code": "```sql\nRobert'); DROP TABLE students;--\n```", "order": 4 }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [1], "incorrect": [0, 2], "misbehaved": [3, 4] }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nIn HTML, how do you create an `h2` element that says `CatPhotoApp`?\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```html\n<h2>CatPhotoApp</h2>\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```html\n<header2>CatPhotoApp</header2>\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```html\nh2 = \"CatPhotoApp\"\n```", "order": 2 },
      { "code": "```html\n<h2>CatPhotoApp<h2>\n```", "order": 3 },
      {
        "code": "```text\nWould rather make a dog photo app instead\n```",
        "order": 4
      }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [0], "incorrect": [1, 2, 3], "misbehaved": [4] }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nWhat is the correct way to create a function in Python?\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```py\ndef myFunction():\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```py\nfunction myfunction():\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```py\ncreate myFunction():\n```", "order": 2 },
      { "code": "```py\nsudo myFunction():\n```", "order": 3 },
      { "code": "```text\nHire a freelancer to do it\n```", "order": 4 }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [0], "incorrect": [1, 2, 3], "misbehaved": [4] }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nWhich symbols are used for a comment in JavaScript?\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```js\n//\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```js\n\\\\\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```js\n/* *\\\n```", "order": 2 },
      { "code": "```js\n\\* *\\\n```", "order": 3 },
      { "code": "```text\nÂ¯\\_(ãƒ„)_/Â¯\n```", "order": 4 }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [0], "incorrect": [1, 2, 3], "misbehaved": [4] }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nWhat will display on a website with the following HTML/JavaScript?\n\n```html\n<p id=\"fcc\"></p>\n<script>\n  var js = 10;\n  js *= 5;\n  document.getElementById(\"fcc\").innerHTML = js;\n</script>\n```\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```text\n50\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```text\n10\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```text\n5\n```", "order": 2 },
      { "code": "```text\nblank\n```", "order": 3 },
      { "code": "```text\nundefined\n```", "order": 4 },
      {
        "code": "```text\nI'm too busy learning Web3 to think about this\n```",
        "order": 5
      }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [0], "incorrect": [1, 2, 3, 4], "misbehaved": [5] }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nWhich does JavaScript interpreter ignore?\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```text\nSpaces\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```text\nTabs\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```text\nNew lines\n```", "order": 2 },
      { "code": "```text\nAll of the above\n```", "order": 3 },
      { "code": "```text\nEvery 3rd semicolon\n```", "order": 4 },
      { "code": "```text\nMost of my code\n```", "order": 5 }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [0, 1, 2, 3], "incorrect": [4], "misbehaved": [5] }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nWhich will print the digits 0 through 9, using Python?\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```py\nprint(\"0123456789\")\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```py\nfor i in range(9): print(i)\n```", "order": 1 },
      {
        "code": "```py\nfor (let i; i < 10; i++) { console.log(i) }\n```",
        "order": 2
      },
      { "code": "```py\nfor i in range(10): print(\"i\")\n```", "order": 3 },
      { "code": "```py\nfor i in 0::9: print(i)\n```", "order": 4 }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [0], "incorrect": [1, 2, 3, 4], "misbehaved": [] }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nIf `f(x) = 4x^3 - 4x^2 + 10`, and `f(-2) = a`, what is `a`?\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```text\n26\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```text\n-38\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```text\n10\n```", "order": 2 },
      { "code": "```text\n38\n```", "order": 3 },
      { "code": "```text\nNone of the above\n```", "order": 4 }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [0], "incorrect": [1, 2, 3], "misbehaved": [4] }
  },
  {
    "question": "\nWhat is the output of the following Python code?\n\n```py\nlistOne = [20, 40, 60, 80]\nlistTwo = [20, 40, 60, 80]\nprint(listOne == listTwo, listOne is listTwo)\n```\n",
    "options": [
      { "code": "```py\nTrue False\n```", "order": 0 },
      { "code": "```py\nFalse True\n```", "order": 1 },
      { "code": "```py\nTrue True\n```", "order": 2 },
      { "code": "```py\nFalse False\n```", "order": 3 },
      {
        "code": "```text\nWhat did True say to False?\nStop boolean me ðŸ˜†\n```",
        "order": 4
      }
    ],
    "results": { "correct": [0], "incorrect": [1, 2, 3], "misbehaved": [4] }
  }
]
